[music]
We are here at the SOS Vida.
An instituition that takes care of special and malnourished children and others with Legal/Justice issues.
[music]
It's been 21 years at this new house
and another 5 years elsewhere, for a total of 26 years.
[music]
We have rescued close to 3.000 children.
We work 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
[music]
We have a total of 20 people in our staff
including psychologists, social services
in addition to many volunteers,
medical doctors,
laboratories, dentists, nutritionists...
All volunteers.
[music]
We dedicate 24 hours to these children.
We currently have 21 children.
But it varies significantly.
Sometimes we have 30 or up to 40 children.
[music]
We are very grateful to all those who
have contributed until now
and those who will continue to help and support
us to rescue these children.
I am grateful from the bottom of my heart!
I know Jesus Christ will bless
all these families who have helped us
and also these children's families in their own homes.
[music]
We need to have an abundace of love to these children, because without love
it would be impossible to accomplish all we need to do for them.